<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project Report</title><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/</link><description>Recent content on Project Report</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/conclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/conclusion/</guid><description> Conclusion # Conclusion about the project What was achieved What can be improved for the capstone project</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/implementation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/implementation/</guid><description> Implementation # Frontend Repository Backend Repository Frontend Repository # Repository # Implementation # Backend Repository # Repository # Backend Repository Implementation #</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/introduction/</guid><description>Introduction # Background and motivation for the project Problem statement and objectives Overview of the low-code platform and its significance in supporting the development of a promotion platform Background and Motivation # In an era characterized by digital transformation and rapid technological advances, the demand for software applications is skyrocketing. However, the traditional software development approach often requires a significant investment of time and resources, creating barriers for businesses, especially small to medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), that lack these resources.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/literature-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/literature-review/</guid><description>Literature Review # Review of existing low-code platforms and their features Exploration of related technologies and frameworks Analysis of similar projects or research in the field Existing Low-code Development Platforms Comparion # Low-code Developing is slowly becoming a thing in business environment. And to keep up with the demand, many low-code development platforms have been provided for the business users with a large variety of usage and pricing. Yet, we would like to introduce 3 platforms that we consider the most notable ones.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/methodology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/methodology/</guid><description>Methodology # Description of the development methodology employed Overview of the technologies, tools, and frameworks used Development Methodology # Development Approach Task Management Version Control Developement Approach # The project&amp;rsquo;s development approach is based on the Agile methodology, but does not follow strictly to any existing framework. Some of the main principles of the Agile methodology that will be followed are:
Each team member shares the same responsibilities and has the same authority.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/project-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/project-management/</guid><description>Project Management # Overview of project planning and scheduling Discussion of project milestones and deliverables Reflection on team collaboration and coordination Lessons learned and recommendations for future projects Project Planning and Scheduling # Project Timeline # The project begins from 11/09/2023 and is expect to lasts 15 weeks until 19/12/2023. The project is divided into 3 phases, each of which lasts 5 weeks. The phases are as follows:
Phase 1: Requirement Analysis Phase 2: System Design Phase 3: Implementation Phase 4: Testing and Deployment Two major milestones are set for the project:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/requirement-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/requirement-analysis/</guid><description>Requirement Analysis # Identification and documentation of functional and non-functional requirements Use cases and user stories for the low-code platform Discussion of expectations and limitations of the project Actor # Developer: include citizen developers and technical developers who create application by platform Example: developers, system engineers, business employees in different departments like sales, marketing, etc. External database, CMS Third-party Provider Requirements # Functional requirements # For Developer (User) # The platform provides lowcode UI or drag-n-drop interface for users to interact with when editing or customizing</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/system-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/system-design/</guid><description>System Design # High-level architecture of the low-code platform Explanation of the chosen architectural style Description of the key components and their interactions Detailed design of each microservice and its responsibilities High-Level Architecture # Architectural Style # Arcchitecture style is the fundamental structural design of a software system. It consists of a set of patterns and principles used to define the system&amp;rsquo;s components, their interactions, and the constraints that guide their design and evolution.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/testing-and-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nguyendhst.github.io/HK231-Specialized-Project/testing-and-evaluation/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>